aioboards.com 2011-01-12

# Privacy Policy - AIO Boards - All in One Forums

Aio Boards's Privacy Policy  
---  
  
  * Aio Boards recognizes that you care about the personal information that is held about you and how that is used.
  * This privacy policy applies to all personal data, submitted by you, to the Aio Boards web site.
  * By registering to Aio Boards you need to submit a chosen name and contact information, more specifically an e-mail address. No extremely personal information, such as Social Security or Credit Card numbers are stored by us.
  * Aio Boards also stores and reads cookies to and from your computer. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our forums and general website features to recognize your browser for when you return to this web site. By using this website, you agree that both the webserver, and any trusted 3rd party we chose, such as advertising networks, may place a tracking cookie on your machine and access it at any time during your session. In general, cookies are safe and are not a security issue when being used from 'trusted' internet sites, such as Aio Boards. For information on how to manage cookies in your browser, please visit [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=2)
  * Aio Boards will not sell, transmit or distribute any data held without your prior permission or consent, unless required to do so under relevant United States legislation.
  * All other information provided by you goes into a "public profile" and is entirely optional, all information held in that profile is held there at your own risk. This info is edited via your Control Panel in the forums.
  * You have a legal right for the personal information held at Aio Boards to be updated if it is incorrect or deleted if you choose. Most of this can be done through your Control Panel in the forums. If you are having issues with this, please contact us if you need help.
  * Aio Boards will take all reasonable effort to ensure that all personal information about you submitted is maintained secure on our server. However, we make no warranty to this.
  * This site is intended for individuals over the age of 13. Any information collected is intended to be of individuals over the age of 13. According to [COPPA](http://www.ftc.gov/coppa/index.html), our site does NOT cater to children. "Operators of commercial websites or online services directed to children under 13 that collect personal information from children" require a COPPA agreement and privacy policy. Since we do not cater to this age group, no COPPA exists on Aio Boards
  * This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice. It is your responsibility to check this page for updates or changes. If you have any questions regarding your privacy, then [Contact Us](http://www.aioboards.com/contact-us/)

Aio Boards's DMCA Privacy Policy  
---  
  
  * Aio Boards, is in compliance with 17 U.S.C. § 512 and the Digital Millennium Copyright Act ("DMCA"). It is our policy to respond to any infringement notices and take appropriate actions under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act ("DMCA") and other applicable intellectual property laws. If your copyrighted material has been posted on Aio Boards.Com or if links to your copyrighted material are returned through our search engine and you want this material removed, you must provide a written communication that details the information listed in the following section. Please be aware that you will be liable for damages (including costs and attorneys' fees) if you misrepresent information listed on our site that is infringing on your copyrights. We suggest that you first contact an attorney for legal assistance on this matter. The following elements must be included in your copyright infringement
  
Claim : 
  * Provide evidence of the authorized person to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
  * Provide sufficient contact information so that we may contact you. You must also include a valid email address.
  * You must identify in sufficient detail the copyrighted work claimed to have been infringed and including at least one search term under which the material appears in Aio Boards.com' search results.
  * A statement that the complaining party has a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law.
  * A statement that the information in the notification is accurate, and under penalty of perjury, that the complaining party is authorized to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly infringed.
  * Must be signed by the authorized person to act on behalf of the owner of an exclusive right that is allegedly being infringed. You can send us the infringement notice **[Here](http://www.aioboards.com/contact-us/)**. Please allow up to a week for an email response.
  
***NOTE***  

  * Note that emailing your complaint to other parties such as our Internet Service Provider will not expedite your request and may result in a delayed response due the complaint not properly being filed.

All times are GMT +1. The time now is 04:34 PM.
